arcsoft.com 2014-07-04

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to ArcSoft. We've developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. This Privacy Policy governs your use of the ArcSoft web site at www.arcsoft.com, and all associated sites linked to www.arcsoft.com by ArcSoft, its agents and affiliates, including ArcSoft sites around the world (collectively, "Site") and all other services provided to you by ArcSoft (collectively, "Service"). The terms "you," "your," and "user" refer to the user of our Service. The terms "ArcSoft," "we," "us," and "our" refer to ArcSoft. By using the Service, you consent to the data practices prescribed in this statement. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Service following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the changes. 

##  Collection and Use of Personal Information 

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you use the Service or in contact with ArcSoft or our affiliates. ArcSoft and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. Here are some examples of the types of personal information ArcSoft may collect and how we may use it. 

##  What personal information we collect 

When you register an ArcSoft account, register your products, purchase a product, download a software update, participate in an online contest, communicate with us through email or phone, or otherwise use our Service, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, device, location, age and occupation. 

##  How we use your personal information 

The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on ArcSoft's latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. 

We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. 

We may also use the information that you provide to respond to your requests, support your use of ArcSoft products and services, or customize future shopping for you. 

From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. 

We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve ArcSoft's products, services, and customer communications. 

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our Service. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you and we may use the information you provide to administer those programs. 

##  Cookies and Other Technologies 

ArcSoft and our affiliates may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons, and other technologies while providing the Service. When you access the ArcSoft Service, we may obtain and store certain types of information such as your IP address, time and date of access, language use, the type of browser used and the page(s) you request. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our Service people have used, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements. 

If you want to disable cookies, you can do so by modifying the browser settings. Check with your browser provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note that certain features of the ArcSoft Service will not be available once cookies are disabled. 

##  Information That is Publicly Available 

When you create an ArcSoft account and use the ArcSoft Service, some information about your ArcSoft account and your account activity may be provided to other users of the Service. This may include the date and time you opened your account, the date and time you last logged into your account, and the number of messages you have posted to the forum. 

Your ArcSoft forum nickname, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on ArcSoft Site, such as when you post messages to ArcSoft forum. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the forum. 

Any image, text and information that you submit to the ArcSoft Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. You are responsible for the information you choose to submit to the Site in these instances. 

##  Disclosure to Third Parties 

At times ArcSoft may make certain personal information available to third-party affiliates that work with ArcSoft to provide products and services, or that help ArcSoft market to customers. Personal information will only be shared by ArcSoft to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. You may request to not having your information submitted to such affiliates by contacting ArcSoft Support (http://www.arcsoft.com/support). ArcSoft will not sell, lease, share or otherwise use your personal information except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

ArcSoft may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary: (1) to comply with any law, legal process, and/or requests from government authorities within or outside your country of residence; (2) to protect and defend the rights or property of ArcSoft; (3) to enforce our Terms of Service; (4) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of ArcSoft, the operation of the Service or the general public; or (5) for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate. 

Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party. 

##  Protection of Personal Information 

ArcSoft takes precautions, including administrative, technical, and physical measures, to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. 

The online services offered by ArcSoft and its affiliates use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on web pages where personal information is collected (for example, credit card and other payment information). To use these services, we recommend you use an SSL-enabled browser such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, or Safari. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it's transmitted over the Internet. 

##  Integrity and Retention of Personal Information 

ArcSoft makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

##  Access to Personal Information 

If you have an ArcSoft account, you may update or correct your personal profile information at any time by visiting your account profile page. 

For other personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access and support so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate, or delete the data if ArcSoft is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. Please contact ArcSoft customer support ([http://www.arcsoft.com/support](http://www.arcsoft.com/support/)) for such request. If you do not want to receive any marketing or promotional email from ArcSoft, you can either choose the opt-out option where it is available or contact ArcSoft customer support ([http://www.arcsoft.com/support](http://www.arcsoft.com/support/)). 

##  Children 

The Service is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 13. We require that use of the Service and all purchases made through it be by individuals who are 13 years of age or older. ArcSoft does not permit registration by and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13. If ArcSoft learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible. 

##  Third-Party Sites and Services 

This Privacy Policy applies only to information ArcSoft collects about you as a user of ArcSoft Service. This policy does not apply to information about you collected by third party web sites and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from ArcSoft Service. The information collected or obtained by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies. Additionally, in the event you access a service using ArcSoft Service which is co-branded with a third party such third party's privacy policy, in addition to the ArcSoft Privacy Policy, may also apply. 

Please note that ArcSoft may utilize a third-party e-commerce service provider to manage its online store and the transactions related to that service. The information collected by such third-party e-commerce service provider during the transaction process is subject to their own privacy policies, and not this Privacy Policy. However, ArcSoft will also have access to the information that you provided to such third-party e-commerce service provider. 

##  International Users 

Information you provide may be transferred or accessed by ArcSoft, its agents, and affiliates around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. By using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country except in the case of data transfers from the EEA and Switzerland, which are covered under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks. 

ArcSoft complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. ArcSoft has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, ArcSoft commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact ArcSoft at [legal@arcsoft.com](mailto:legal@arcsoft.com). 

ArcSoft has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Safe Harbor, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by ArcSoft, please visit the BBB EU Safe Harbor web site at www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint. 

##  Your California Privacy Rights 

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request to [legal@arcsoft.com](mailto:legal@arcsoft.com). 

##  Privacy Questions 

If you have questions or concerns about ArcSoft's Privacy Policy, please contact us at [legal@arcsoft.com](mailto:legal@arcsoft.com). 

_Last updated: October 8, 2013_
